This traditional stretch is called the Twisted Pretzel.
Now it may sound intimidating but it's a great stretch for your back, your hips, overall stretch.
So come on down to your mat.
And you want to just have your feet on the floor, your knees are bent.
Take your left leg and cross it over your right leg.
Then take your left foot and hook it behind your right ankle as you lift your feet up off the floor.
Now, take your arms out like a T and then gently roll your knees over to the left side.
Turn your head to the right side.
You want to make sure that you're keeping your shoulder blades on the mat.
And just breathe nice and easy, holding the stretch for about thirty seconds.
And then engage your abdominal muscles, lifting your knees up and then twist over to the other side.
And you want to try to get your knees all the way over.
Close your eyes, hold that position for about thirty seconds and then come on up and then switch legs.
Taking the right over left, hooking and then coming over to the side.
And that is your Twisted Pretzel.